So let's talk about the skills you need to get and keep a job.
If you want to impress your boss, you'll need three types of skills.
First, you'll need some kind of talent.
La la la la la la.
You develop your talent or skills through education,
training, and experience.
Then there are employability skills.
These include communication, problem solving, positive attitude,
adaptability, the ability to work with others.
These are key to getting and keeping a job you love.
Can you multitask, plan large projects, work well with others?
You know you can.
Finally, there's enterprise and skills.
These are not only important to entrepreneurs.
Everyone can benefit from having enterprise and skills.
The ability to be creative, take initiative,
try new things, lead a team, learn from mistakes, and find new solutions.
With your talent and skills, you'll enter the job market.
Here, you'll also need to understand the forces of supply and demand.